Thank you so much.
I gave SpaceX less than a 10% chance of succeeding at all
to be clear.
In fact, I told people this.
Look, we're probably going to fail,
but we should give it a try because if we don't,
if there's not a new company that enters space,
we will never be a truly space-bearing civilization.
And while the other aerospace companies,
they build good rockets and everything,
they were simply not pursuing the technology that's necessary
to make life multi-planetary, to make Star Trek,
to make the exciting science fiction
futures that we've read about real.
And that's what SpaceX is all about,
is to take the fiction out of science fiction
and create an exciting, inspiring future for everyone.
SpaceX wants to be able to take you to the moon,
take you to Mars, and ultimately beyond.
And I'm confident at this point that with the incredible team
that we have here at SpaceX, that we will do that for you.
There are always problems on Earth.
There are always things that we wish to be better,
that we want to solve here on Earth.
And we should solve them.
But there also have to be things that
get you excited about the future,
that make you glad to wake up in the morning,
because you can't wait to see what happens next.
And that's the future that SpaceX wants to bring to you.